zendasworld.org 2011-11-20

# jaroo.com

We're glad you dropped in! Cookie Jar welcomes you to our Jaroo website.

The Jaroo site has been created for your personal entertainment, education, and information, so please feel free to explore it. While you're here, we want you to be aware that access to this site implies your full understanding of our respective legal rights and obligations. Use of this site is subject to the terms of service, below, as well as all applicable laws. Our terms of service are legally binding and govern your use of this site, so please read them carefully.

Your Acceptance of Terms of Service:   
The Jaroo website is a proprietary online service offered by Cookie Jar Entertainment. Cookie Jar reserves the right, at its discretion, to modify, add, or remove portions of these terms at any time. If you do not agree with any of these terms of use, please do not access the Jaroo site, as your use indicates your agreement to these terms of service. Please check these terms periodically for changes. Your continued use of this site following the posting of changes to these terms constitutes your agreement with those changes.

Use of Materials Contained on this Site:   
Cookie Jar Entertainment respects and honors the intellectual property rights of others and asks that all users of this site do the same. This site and all content incorporated within it contains material that is derived in whole or in part from material provided by Cookie Jar Entertainment, and other sources, and is protected by U.S. and international copyright and trademark laws, and other proprietary rights. The characters, logos, and other images are also protected as registered or unregistered trademarks, trade names, and/or service marks owned by Cookie Jar Entertainment and others. No material may be copied, reproduced, republished, or redistributed in any way, other than for your personal, non-commercial use, provided you keep intact all copyright and trademark notices. Modification of the materials or use of the materials for any other purpose is a violation of Cookie Jar's and other sources' copyright, trademark and other proprietary rights. The use of any such materials on any other web site or networked computer environment without Cookie Jar's express written consent is prohibited. Your right to make use of this site and the material or other content appearing on it is subject to your assent to the terms of service. Modification or use of the content on this site for any purpose not permitted by these terms is prohibited. We are dedicated to protecting your privacy and handling any personal information we obtain from you with care and respect. Because we are a media company that deals with tween and teens, we particularly value the safety of our website visitors who are under 13, and we recognize the need to provide additional protections for them.

This Privacy Policy details the measures taken by Cookie Jar Entertainment to protect your privacy in connection with your use of Jaroo.com. We request that all guests take the time to review the information in this section to familiarize themselves with our policies and to answer their questions regarding our privacy policies and principles.

PRIVACY POLICY OVERVIEW  
We have taken significant efforts to develop our privacy policies in compliance with the requirements established by the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act ("COPPA"). COPPA requires that we inform parents and legal guardians ("parents") about how we collect, use, and disclose personal information from our website visitors who are under 13 years of age ("kids"), and that we obtain a parent's consent before we collect any personal information from kids. By personal information, we mean individually identifiable information about a user that we collect online, such as first and last name, physical or email address, or telephone number.

COOKIES  
When guests visit our site, we may automatically collect, in a text file called a "cookie," certain non-personally identifiable information about the guest's computer, such as the operating system that the guest is using (for example, Windows 95 or Mac OS), the user's IP address (this is the automatic number that is assigned to your computer when you surf the Internet), the web browser the guest is using (for example, Netscape Navigator or Microsoft Internet Explorer), and information about the Internet Service Provider (for example, AOL or MSN).

We collect and analyze this site usage information in the aggregate, using the cookies to help us figure out how many people visit our sites, which of our web pages they visit, and how long they stay there. By showing how and when visitors use the website, cookies help us to see which areas are popular and which are not. We can then use this information to create a website that better serves the needs of our guests.

For a user, cookies make web surfing easier by enabling us to save the user's passwords, purchases, and preferences. A cookie lets the computer remember that a user has registered, which allows us to speed up the user's future activities at our website. If you leave the site and then return, cookies will tell us information that you have already provided so that you do not have to start all over again. Letting the cookie do the recordkeeping saves the user the trouble of entering information over and over again during a single visit.

Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies. If you would prefer, you can set your browser to refuse cookies, or to alert you whenever cookies are being sent. However, it is possible that some areas of Jaroo.com will not function properly if you set your computer to refuse cookies.

Although the pieces of information that we collect via cookies are linked to your computer, we do not combine them with any personally identifiable or online contact information, such as a name, address or email address, and therefore you and your family remain anonymous.

You may occasionally get cookies from our ad server and/or from third party advertisers. The ad server cookie is only used to track how frequently each ad appears. No personally identifiable information is stored on the ad server cookie. Jaroo.com does not control the cookies of our ad server and/or third party advertisers, and therefore these cookies are not subject to the Jaroo.com cookie policy. The use of advertising cookies sent by ad servers or third party advertisers is standard in the Internet industry, and you'll find cookies at most major websites.

Jaroo.com does not use "third-party cookies" - cookies that communicate data about users to advertising clearinghouses which, in turn, share that data with other online marketers.

COLLECTION OF INFORMATION BY THIRD-PARTY SITES AND SPONSORS  
Our site contains links to other sites whose privacy policies may be different than our own. We do not endorse or take responsibility for the content or business practices of these sites. Users should visit and read the privacy policies of these other sites, because these sites are not covered by our privacy policy and they may follow procedures that are different than our own.

Jaroo.com will never give a third party your email address or other personal information, except as described in the two paragraphs immediately above (for example, to a contest fulfillment house, or as required by law). However, if you visit a third-party website and choose to opt-in to register with one of our partners or sponsors - or if you neglect to opt-out when given the opportunity - you have allowed this third party to collect your registration information, including your email address.

SECURITY  
Cookie Jar Entertainment has put in place the appropriate procedures to prevent against unauthorized access to our Jaroo.com databases to ensure that the personal information we collect from our visitors remains secure. We have security measures in place to attempt to protect against the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information that our guests provide to us. Although we will exercise reasonable care in providing secure transmission of information between your computer and our servers, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information transmitted to us over the Internet and we accept no liability for any unintentional disclosure.

EFFECTIVE DATE AND AMENDMENTS  
The Privacy Policy described above is effective as of September 15, 2009. Jaroo.com reserves the right to amend its Privacy Policy at any time at its sole discretion. We will notify parents of registered users of material changes in our Privacy Policy, and will post the new policy on Jaroo.com with the effective date of the change clearly marked. If you have concerns about your privacy on the Internet and, particularly, on our site, we suggest that you check back frequently to review any changes to this policy that may affect you.

YOUR ACCEPTANCE OF THESE TERMS  
By using this website, you signify your consent to and agreement with our Jaroo.com Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to all of the terms and conditions of this policy, you should not use our website. The website's content and features may be changed or supplemented at any time as described above. At the end of the Privacy Policy, we indicate the date on which the policy was last updated. Except where material changes in this policy will require us to obtain new parental consent, your continued use of the website after the posting of changes will indicate your acceptance of and agreement to such changes. If, at any time, you do not agree with all of the terms and conditions of the Privacy Policy, you should contact us immediately as described below with your username, your email address, and your zip code, and instruct us to terminate your account, at which time we will do so and delete your account from our database. Any parental or guardian consent provided to COOKIE JAR ENTERTAINMENT will be deemed to apply to the revised Privacy Policy and new or modified features of the website as a whole, unless there is a material change in the data we collect, the manner in which we collect such data, or our data use or disclosure practices, in which case we will obtain a new consent.

QUESTIONS OR CONCERNS? CONTACT US!

If you have any questions or concerns about our Privacy Policy and practices, please contact us.  
You can send us an email at [cpo@thecookiejarcompany.com](mailto:cpo@thecookiejarcompany.com) or you can write to us at Jaroo.com (c/o Cookie Jar Entertainment), 4100 West Alameda Avenue, Burbank, CA 91505
